<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="net.sf.eclipse.tomcat.feature"
      label="Eclipse Tomcat Management Feature"
      version="9.1.4">

   <description url="https://sourceforge.net/projects/tomcatplugin/">
      This Feature enables for simple management of a tomcat server within the Eclipse IDE without the need for the full Web Tools Platform installed.
   </description>

   <license url="https://opensource.org/licenses/MIT">
      Copyright 2014-2018 Markus Keunecke

      The MIT License

      Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software
      and associated documentation files (the &quot;Software&quot;), to deal in the Software without restriction,
      including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute,
      sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
      furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:

      The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all copies or 
      substantial portions of the Software.

      THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED &quot;AS IS&quot;, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING
      UT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND
      NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM,
      DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
      OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.
   </license>

   <url>
      <update label="Tomcat Plugin Update Site" url="http://tomcatplugin.sf.net/update"/>
      <discovery label="Original Plugin Version" url="http://www.eclipsetotale.com/tomcatPlugin.html"/>
   </url>

   <plugin
         id="net.sf.eclipse.tomcat"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
